(Penny:)Please show us?
Please?
(Leonard:)No.
You know I'm gonna read it
either way.
AMY (scoffs):
Good luck finding it.
(gasps)
(Amy:)Amelia and...
(Amy:)the time-trav...
Found it!
(chuckles)
"It was just past dawn
on the prairie,
"and like every morning,
"Amelia prepared
to do her chores.
(Penny:)Except something about
this morning felt different."
(Penny:)Why?
Why did it
feel different?
"Maybe it was the first whisper
of winter in the air,
"or maybe it was
the unconscious handsome man
"with porcelain skin
and curious clothing
"she was about to discover
lying in the field.
"A man who would
open her mind
"to new possibilities
and her body to new feelings."
(Penny and Bernadette squealing)
(Amy:)You know, there was a time when
I was alone and had no friends.
(Amy:)I'm starting to miss that.